Finding Aid for A. Alfred Taubman papers, 1942-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Shopping Centers/Commercial Development 1956-2009
  - Eastridge (San Jose, CA)
    - Property Acquisition and Development
      - San Jose
        - Site Information 1966-1974 (Box 2)
        - Demographic Studies (Box 2)
        - Eastridge Square (Box 2)
        - Valley Creek Proposed Project (Box 2)
        - Valley Fair/Stevens Creek Plaza Project (Box 2)
      - Agreements (Box 3)
      - Architectural (Box 3)
      - Assessments (Box 3)
      - Construction Costs (Box 3)
      - County of Santa Clara (Box 3)
      - Eastridge Apartments (Box 3)
      - Eastridge Square (Box 3)
      - Expansion (Box 3)
      - Financial (Box 3)
      - Financial, East San Jose Properties (Box 3)
      - Financing (Box 3)
      - Hillview Golf Course (Box 3)
      - Homart (Box 3)
      - Ice Arena (Box 3)
      - Insurance (Box 3)
      - King & Tully Gulf Oil Co. (Box 4)
      - Landscape (Box 4)
      - Leasing (Box 4)
      - Partnership (Box 4)
      - Plans (Box 4)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 4)
      - J.C. Penney 1966-1971, 5 folders (Box 5)
      - Macy's 1965-1971, 4 folders (Box 5)
      - Offering Memorandum; Lease Form (Box 5)
      - Photographs (Box 5)
      - Santa Clara County (Box 5)
      - Sears Roebuck (Box 5)
      - Tassi Property (Box 5)
      - Teacher's Insurance Mortgage (Box 5)
      - White & Tully (intersection of) (Box 5)
      - General Cinema (Box 6)
      - Economic Projections / Marketing Study (Box 6)
      - Liberty House and Rhodes Lease Discussion (Box 6)
      - Property Acquisitions (Box 6)
      - Traffic Considerations (Box 6)
      - News Articles, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Leases and Tenant Files
      - Albert Hayes (Box 7)
      - Albert's Hosiery #2 (Box 7)
      - Allen Shoes (Box 7)
      - Alley (The), International Cafes, Inc. (Box 7)
      - Andrew's Pants (Box 7)
      - Anita Shops (Box 7)
      - Anna Miller's Allied Outlets (Box 7)
      - Arts International (Box 7)
      - B. Dalton Company (Box 7)
      - Bank of America (Box 7)
      - Beef Block, The (Box 7)
      - Big Wig Boutique (Box 7)
      - Birdie's Toy House, Luhn & Sons (Box 7)
      - Bumbleberry Parlor (Box 7)
      - Bresler's (Box 7)
      - Burt's Shoes, Edison (Box 7)
      - Casual Corner (Box 7)
      - Chess King, Inc. (Box 7)
      - Christopher's Flowers (Box 7)
      - Cinderella Wig (Box 7)
      - Citizens Federal Savings & Loan (Box 7)
      - Clothes Barn, The (Box 7)
      - Crocker-Citizens, Crown Jewelers, A. Hirsh and Son, Inc. (Box 7)
      - Dekalb, Peter R., Harlan L. Cady (Box 8)
      - Disro Records (Box 8)
      - Don's Shoe Clinic, Domenic Didomenico (Box 8)
      - Down to Earth (Box 8)
      - E&M Specialties (Box 8)
      - Eastpoint, Okida (Box 8)
      - Earring House (Box 8)
      - Edison Brothers, Size 5-7-9 Shop (Box 8)
      - Farrell's Ice Cream Parlor (Box 8)
      - Fidelity Savings & Loan (Box 8)
      - First National Bank of San Jose (Box 8)
      - Flagg Bros. Shoes, Genesco (Box 8)
      - Florsheim (Box 8)
      - Foxwood, Inc. (Box 8)
      - Frederick's of Hollywood (Box 8)
      - French Cafes (Box 8)
      - Gallenkamp, Inc. (Box 8)
      - Gap, The (Box 8)
      - Gardner's (Wohl) Bootery (Box 8)
      - Golden West Savings (Box 8)
      - Granat (Box 8)
      - Grodins (Box 8)
      - Hardy Shoes, Genesco (Box 8)
      - Harold's Shoes C.T. & R West, Inc. (Box 8)
      - Hickory Farms (Box 8)
      - Hip Pocket, Lord Rebel, Ind. (Box 8)
      - Hot Sam, Cal Pretzels, Inc. (Box 8)
      - House of Cards (Box 8)
      - House of Fabrics (Box 8)
      - IMP Imports (Box 8)
      - J.K. Gill Co. (Box 8)
      - Jarman Shoes, Genesco (Box 8)
      - Kay Jewelry (Box 8)
      - King Norman's Kingdom of Toys (Box 8)
      - Kinney Shoes (Box 8)
      - Kushins (Box 8)
      - La Joya Manufacturing Jewelers (Box 9)
      - Lafayette Coney Island (Box 9)
      - Lane Bryant (Box 9)
      - Leed's (Edison Bros.) (Box 9)
      - Lerner Shops (Box 9)
      - Liberty House (Rhodes Western) (Box 9)
      - Love Is, International Cafes, Inc. (Box 9)
      - Lucky Stores (Box 9)
      - Macy's, Penney's (Box 9)
      - (Joseph) Magnin Co. (Box 9)
      - Marcus Stevens Creek (Box 9)
      - Mary Moo (Box 9)
      - Merle Norman Cosmetics (Box 9)
      - Miller's Intern. (Box 9)
      - Morrow's Nut House (Box 9)
      - Nobby Knits (Box 9)
      - Motherhood Maternity (Box 9)
      - National Uniform (Box 9)
      - Naturalizer Shoes (Box 9)
      - Nature Food Centres (Box 9)
      - Orange Bowl (Box 9)
      - Patti's Chinese Kitchen (Box 9)
      - Persian Bazaar (Box 9)
      - Pescadero Casual (Box 9)
      - Pine Tree Candies (Box 9)
      - Plum Tree, The (Box 9)
      - Rebel Shop Lord, Rebel Ind. (Box 10)
      - Red Carpet Restaurant (Box 10)
      - Red Cross Shoes (Box 10)
      - Roberta's (Box 10)
      - Rodder's (Box 10)
      - Roos/Atkins (Box 10)
      - Round Table Pizza (Box 10)
      - Royal Coachman Joseph Shemueli (Box 10)
      - Sabek, Inc. (Box 10)
      - San Jose Apparel (Petrie's) (Box 10)
      - Sand, (R. H. & C. I.) (Box 10)
      - Santa Cruz Import (Box 10)
      - Sarkowsky, Fred & Barbara J. (Box 10)
      - Sears Cafeteria (Box 10)
      - See's Candies (Box 10)
      - Sherman Clay (Box 10)
      - Shaver's World (Box 10)
      - Shelly's Cocktail Lounge (Stan Shell, Inc.) (Box 10)
      - Shreve & Co (Dayton-Hudson) (Box 10)
      - Silber's (Box 10)
      - Singer Co. (Box 10)
      - 1601 Albany Ave. Blvd Corp. (Box 10)
      - Smith's Clothiers, 2 folders (Box 10)
      - Sommer & Kaufmann (Genesco) (Box 10)
      - Studio Support (Box 10)
      - Sunglass, The (Box 10)
      - Sunset House (Box 10)
      - Sunvalley Imports (Box 10)
      - Susie's Casuals (Box 10)
      - Thayer McNeil (Box 10)
      - Tie Rack Store (Box 10)
      - Tiffany's Bakeries (Box 10)
      - Tinderbox, The (Box 10)
      - Topps & Trowsers (Box 10)
      - United Travel Serv. A. V. Constantine (Box 10)
      - Walden Book Co. (Box 11)
      - Wax Tree, The (Box 11)
      - Weisfield's, Inc. (Box 11)
      - Wells Fargo Bank (Box 11)
      - Wicks N' Sticks (Box 11)
      - Woman's Shop (Box 11)
      - F. W. Woolworth (Box 11)
      - World's Fare
        - Alfinito & Wong (Box 11)
        - Do-Nut (Box 11)
        - Fish N' Chip (Box 11)
        - Hofbrau (Box 11)
        - Italian (Box 11)
        - Kathy's Hamburger (Box 11)
        - Pepe's (Box 11)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 11)
  - Hilltop (Richmond, CA)
    - Agreements (Box 12)
    - Architectural (Box 12)
    - Budget (Box 12)
    - Construction (Box 12)
    - Demographics and Traffic (Box 12)
    - Eastdil Realty, Inc. (Box 12)
    - Federated Department Store (Box 12)
    - Financial (Box 12)
    - Grand Opening (Box 12)
    - Lease Requests (Box 12)
    - Litigation (Box 13)
    - Logo (Box 13)
    - Macy's (Box 13)
    - News Articles (Box 13)
    - J.C. Penney (Box 13)
    - Philip Lyon, Gordon and Company (Box 13)
    - Photographs (Box 13)
    - Progress Reports (Box 13)
    - Projections (Box 13)
    - Prospective Tenants (Box 13)
    - Public Relations (Box 13)
    - Residual Property (Box 13)
    - Sales Analysis (Box 13)
    - Sears (Box 13)
    - Sculpture (Box 13)
    - Tax (Box 13)
    - Theatres (Box 13)
  - Southland (Hayward, CA)
    (includes Palma Ceia and Southland Square)
    - Palma Ceia
      (the name was changed to Southland in 1963 following its sale to AAT in 1962)
      - Articles and Photographs (Box 14)
      - Budget Cost Estimate and Outline Specification (Box 14)
      - Chase Manhattan Bank Loans (Box 14)
      - Correspondence and Other Documents 1962 (Box 14)
      - Financial Statements (Box 14)
      - Leasing Information (Box 14)
      - Public Relations / Name Change (Box 14)
      - Purchase Agreement for Sale of Palma Ceia from Arthur Rubloff to A.A. Taubman 1962 (Box 14)
    - Palma Ceia Phase III
      - Architectural (Box 14)
      - Leasing (Box 14)
    - Southland
      - Brochures (Box 14)
      - Design planning: Raymond Loewy/William Snaith, Inc. (Box 14)
      - Hayward (Calif.), material about (Box 14)
      - J.C. Penney Co. Specification (Box 14)
      - Photographs (Box 14)
      - Study: "The Dynamic Growth of South San Francisco Bay Area" (Box 14)
      - Architectural Plans (Box 15)
      - Specifications (Box 15)
      - Public Relations (Box 15)
    - Pioneer Savings and Loan Plans (Box 16)
    - Phase III
      - Artworks (Box 16)
    - Architecture, General (Box 16)
    - Christmas (Box 16)
    - Donald G. Clever Design (Box 16)
    - Dun & Bradstreet Reports (Box 16)
    - Easements (Box 16)
    - Food Purveyors Council, Inc. By-Laws (Box 16)
    - Friedman, Nathan J. (Box 16)
    - City of Hayward (Box 16)
    - Kenneth Drake Associates Statements (Box 16)
    - Legal, General (Box 16)
    - Legal, Name Change (Box 16)
    - Phase II
      - John Pappas Personal (Box 244)
        [Restricted until Jan. 1, 2082 ]
      - Tidewater Oil Co. (Box 16)
    - Phase IV
      - Rhodes Western (Box 16)
      - Third Department Store (Box 16)
      - Goodyear Rubber (Box 16)
      - Thayer-McNeil (Box 16)
      - Leasing (Box 16)
      - Livingston (Box 16)
    - Phase II
      - Architect (Box 16)
      - Area Calculation Survey (Box 16)
      - Leasing (Box 16)
      - Legal (Box 16)
      - Operations (Box 16)
    - Phase III
      - Projections (Box 16)
    - Phase II: Accounting Statement (Box 17)
    - Phase III
      - Operations (Box 17)
      - Utilities (Box 17)
      - Opening (Box 17)
    - Prospective Tenants (Box 17)
    - Phase III
      - Mechanical (Box 17)
    - Eden Square
      - Wells Fargo (Box 17)
      - Architectural (Box 17)
      - Development (Box 17)
      - Financial (Box 17)
      - General (Box 17)
      - Leasing (Box 17)
      - Legal (Box 17)
    - Apartments Adjacent to Southland (Box 17)
    - Phase IV, Proposed Theatre (Box 17)
    - Public Relations (Box 17)
    - American Savings and Loan (Box 18)
    - Architectural (Box 18)
    - Cinema I and II (Box 18)
    - City of Hayward (Box 18)
    - Construction Costs (Box 18)
    - Contracts (Box 18)
    - Diamond Jim Restaurant (Box 18)
    - Equitable (Box 18)
    - Financing (Box 18)
    - First State Bank (Box 18)
    - Insurance (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 18)
    - Plans (Box 18)
    - Projections (Box 18)
    - Public Relations (Box 18)
    - Sears (Box 18)
    - Sears Data Processing Building (Box 18)
    - Southland Square Professional Building (Box 18)
    - Utilities (Box 18)
    - Wells Fargo (Box 18)
    - Phase III
      - General (Box 19)
      - Mall Kiosks (Box 19)
    - Phase I
      - Personnel / Staff
        [Restricted until January 1, 2082 ]
        - General (Box 244)
        - Janet Bennett (Box 244)
        - John Hamilton (Box 244)
        - Avner Naggar (Box 244)
        - John H. Smeddle (Box 244)
      - Sears Roebuck & Co. (Box 20)
      - Shopping Center Utilities, Inc. (Box 20)
      - Taubman, A. Alfred (miscellaneous) (Box 20)
      - Traffic Control (Box 20)
    - Phase III
      - Architectural, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Chase Manhattan Bank Draw (Box 20)
      - Construction (Box 20)
      - Construction Costs Estimates (Box 20)
      - Construction "Exhibit A" (Box 20)
      - Construction "Exhibit B" (Box 20)
      - Construction Photographs (Box 20)
      - Contracts and Agreements (Box 20)
      - Design (Box 20)
      - Electrical (Box 20)
      - Fire Alarm (Box 20)
      - Hayward, California (Box 20)
      - Landscaping (Box 20)
      - Leasing-General (Box 20)
      - Leasing Plans (Box 20)
      - Legal (Box 20)
      - J.C. Penney (Box 21)
      - Project Offices (Box 21)
      - Project Signing (Box 21)
      - Sprinkler Alarm System (Box 21)
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous 1964-1969 (Box 22)
    - Letters of Direction 1963-1964 (Box 22)
    - Logo 1963-1964 (Box 22)
    - Milton Meyer & Co. 1964-1965 (Box 22)
    - Model 1963-1964 (Box 22)
    - Operations, Combining II & III 1964-1967 (Box 22)
    - Parking Lot 1964-1966 (Box 22)
    - Paving Plan 1963-1964 (Box 22)
    - Project Sign, Pylon 1963-1965 (Box 22)
    - Property Taxes 1961-1966 (Box 22)
    - Rapid Transit 1963-1967 (Box 22)
    - Rental Income Projection 1963-1964 (Box 22)
    - Specification 1964 (Box 22)
    - Phase III. Sears / Branden Properties (Box 23)
    - Partnership Agreements (Box 23)
    - Partners Life Insurance (Box 23)
    - J.C. Penney's Opening 1964 (Box 23)
    - Photographs, 3 folders (Box 23)
    - Southland Square
      - 1972-1981, 7 folders (Box 24)
      - Lease Requests 1975-1980, 5 folders (Box 24)
      - Sumitomo Bank Building (Box 24)
    - Southland
      - 1972-1981, 7 folders (Box 24)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 24)
    - Southland
      - Financial 1976-1980 (Box 25)
      - Photographs, Tenant Status Reports, Lease Projections (Box 25)
      - Lease Requests 1973-1979, 4 folders (Box 25)
  - Stoneridge (Pleasanton, CA)
    - Stoneridge Shopping Center, 4 folders (Box 26)
  - Sunvalley (Concord, CA)
    - Expansion, 2 folders (Box 27)
    - Financial (Box 27)
    - Lease Requests (Box 27)
    - Lease Synopses (Box 27)
    - Leasing/Tenant Correspondence (Box 27)
    - Legal Action, Hickory Farms/Swiss Colony (Box 28)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 28)
    - Photographs, 1 portfolios; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Plans, 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Plans, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Restructuring and Refinancing March 1989, 3 volumes (in 3 portfolios) (Box 29)
    - Surveys (Box 29)
    - Tenant Status Reports (Box 29)
  - Woodfield (Schaumburg, IL)
    - Agreements, 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Architectural Plan (Box 30)
    - Carson-Pirie-Scott (Box 30)
    - Closing Documents, List of (Box 30)
    - Expansion (Box 30)
    - Federated (Sales Analysis Reports), 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Financial, 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Ground Breaking (Box 30)
    - J. C. Penney (Box 31)
    - Lease (Box 31)
    - Logo (Box 31)
    - Lord & Taylor (Box 31)
    - Marshall-Field (Box 31)
    - Miscellaneous, 4 folders (Box 31)
    - Office Building (Box 31)
    - Photographs (includes Grand Opening), 3 folders (Box 31)
      (see oversize folder for additional photographs)
    - Shopping Center Analysis (Box 31)
    - Projections (Box 32)
    - Public Relations (Box 32)
    - Public Relations, VIP List (Box 32)
    - Residual Property (Box 32)
    - Sears (Box 32)
    - Tenant Reports (Box 32)
    - Tenants
      - Kresge (Box 32)
      - Ice Rink (Box 32)
      - A-F (Box 32)
      - G-L (Box 32)
      - M-R (Box 32)
      - S-Z (Box 32)
  - Briarwood (Ann Arbor, MI)
    - Agreements (Box 33)
    - Architectural (Box 33)
    - Construction (Box 33)
    - Demographics and Traffic Analysis (Box 33)
    - Financial (Box 33)
    - J.L. Hudson Company (Box 33)
    - Logo (Box 33)
    - John McMullen (Box 33)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 33)
    - News Articles (Box 33)
    - Opening (Box 33)
    - J.C. Penney (Box 33)
    - Photographs (Box 33)
    - Plans (Box 33)
    - Preliminary Negotiations (Box 33)
    - Progress Reports (Box 33)
    - Prospective Tenants
      - Tenant Reports (Box 33)
      - A-F (Box 33)
      - G-L (Box 33)
      - M-R (Box 33)
      - S-Z (Box 33)
    - Public Relations (Box 33)
    - Residual Property (Box 33)
    - Sales Analysis (Box 33)
    - Sculpture (Box 33)
    - Sears (Box 33)
    - Taxes (Box 33)
    - Theatres (Box 33)
  - Woodland (Grand Rapids, MI)
    - Topical Files
      - ABC and Calving College Parcels 1975 (Box 34)
      - Amenities and Improvements 1974-1975 (Box 34)
      - Apartments (Box 34)
      - Bank (Box 34)
      - Budget 1975 (Box 34)
      - Eastdil Realty 1974-1975 (Box 34)
      - Executive Committee Meetings 1975-1976 (Box 34)
      - Grand Rapids Taxes (Box 34)
      - J. L. Hudson 1970-1975 (Box 34)
      - Kiosks (Box 34)
      - Kresge Stores 1974-1975 (Box 34)
      - Leasing (Box 34)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 34)
      - Motels and Hotels (Box 34)
      - Office Building (Box 34)
      - Phase II Refinancing 1975 (Box 34)
      - Photographs (Box 34)
      - Preliminary Construction Plans 1974 (Box 34)
      - Projections and sales analysis (Box 34)
      - Prospective Tenants, 4 folders (Box 34)
      - Prudential Partnership (Box 34)
      - Rent Projections 1975 (Box 34)
      - Residual Property 1972-1975 (Box 34)
      - Restaurant (Box 34)
      - Signs (Box 34)
      - Traffic 1971-1976 (Box 34)
      - Wallace-Blakeslee Co. (Box 34)
    - Articles and Publicity (Box 34)
    - Tenant's Files
      - Albert's 1965-1968 (Box 35)
      - Albert's Hosiery 1965-1968 (Box 35)
      - Allied Stores 1965-1966 (Box 35)
      - American Greeting Cards 1967-1968 (Box 35)
      - Barricini Stores 1965-1970 (Box 35)
      - Beverly's 1965-1968 (Box 35)
      - Bond's 1965-1966 (Box 35)
      - Borman Foods 1968-1969 (Box 35)
      - Botany Industries 1966-1968 (Box 35)
      - Brimmer Flower & Gift Gallery 1966-1970 (Box 35)
      - Bulliss (George Bulliss Men's Wear) 1965 (Box 35)
      - Buttercup Bakeries 1966-1970 (Box 35)
      - Cardinal For Her 1966-1970 (Box 35)
      - Cedar Shack 1967 (Box 35)
      - Clippings, Advertising and Sales Promotion Manual (Box 35)
      - Duane Shoes 1968-1969 (Box 35)
      - Duet Shop 1968 (Box 35)
      - Edison Brothers 1965-1967 (Box 35)
      - Fanny Farmer 1968 (Box 35)
      - Flagg 1966 (Box 35)
      - Flaming Pit 1968-1970 (Box 35)
      - Florsheim Shoes 1965-1970 (Box 35)
      - Gannon's Shoes 1967 (Box 35)
      - Gantos 1965-1966 (Box 35)
      - Genesco 1965-1967 (Box 35)
      - Grinnell 1966-1971 (Box 35)
      - Groskopf's 1965-1966 (Box 35)
      - Haig (L.G. Haig Peacock Shoes) 1966-1968 (Box 35)
      - House of Fabrics 1966-1967 (Box 35)
      - House of Nine 1965-1969 (Box 35)
      - Howard Stores 1966 (Box 35)
      - Hudson (J.L. Hudson Co.) 1967-1970 (Box 35)
      - Hughes-Hatcher, G. R. 1966-1968 (Box 35)
      - Ives (Susan Ives Stores) 1965-1966 (Box 35)
      - Kinney (G. R. Kinney) 1965-1968 (Box 35)
      - Kresge (S.S. Kresge Co.) 1965-1970 (Box 35)
      - Lane Bryant 1967-1970 (Box 36)
      - Leed's Ties 1968 (Box 36)
      - Lober's Shoes 1968 (Box 36)
      - Loeks (Jack Loeks Theatres) 1966 (Box 36)
      - Maling's Shoes 1966-1968 (Box 36)
      - Marks (H.A. Marks) 1968 (Box 36)
      - Mason (Robert J. Mason) 1966-1968 (Box 36)
      - MBM 1965-1971 (Box 36)
      - McAn (Thom McAn) 1965-1970 (Box 36)
      - McCrory-McClellan-Green Stores 1965-1966 (Box 36)
      - Motherhood Maternity 1968 (Box 36)
      - Mulberry Bush 1967 (Box 36)
      - National Uniform 1969 (Box 36)
      - Nina 1966-1969 (Box 36)
      - Nobil Shoes 1966-1968 (Box 36)
      - Nu-Vision Optical 1965-1968 (Box 36)
      - Old Kent Bank 1967 (Box 36)
      - One Hour Martinizing 1967-1968 (Box 36)
      - Parkfield 1967 (Box 36)
      - Parklane Hosiery 1965-1966 (Box 36)
      - Penney (J.C. Penney) 1965-1968 (Box 36)
      - Petrie Stores 1965-1968 (Box 36)
      - Post Office 1966-1967 (Box 36)
      - Radio Shack 1967-1970 (Box 36)
      - Remes Drugs 1966-1968 (Box 36)
      - Richman Brothers 1965-1968 (Box 36)
      - Rose Jewelry 1965-1968 (Box 36)
      - Russell Stover 1965-1966 (Box 36)
      - Sarret's 1965-1968 (Box 36)
      - Schensul's Cafeteria 1966-1970 (Box 36)
      - Sears 1964-1970 (Box 36)
      - Siegel Jewelry 1965-1971 (Box 36)
      - Singer 1965-1967 (Box 36)
      - Spencer Gifts 1966-1968 (Box 36)
      - Steketee's 1964-1965 (Box 36)
      - Theatre 1966-1969 (Box 36)
      - Toy Kiosk 1967-1968 (Box 36)
      - Waldenbooks 1966-1967 (Box 36)
      - Weiss & Neuman Shoe Co. 1967 (Box 36)
      - Winkleman 1965-1967 (Box 36)
      - Woodland Optical 1966 (Box 36)
      - Woolworth, F. W. 1965-1966 (Box 36)
      - Wyoming (First National Bank of Wyoming) 1965 (Box 36)
      - Zale Jewelry 1965-1968 (Box 36)
  - Yonkers, NY
    (proposed shopping center)
    - Census Data (Box 37)
    - Census Tract Demographics (Box 37)
    - Getty Square, 3 folders (Box 37)
    - Getty Square Litigation (Box 37)
    - Proposed Shopping Center
      - General, 10 folders (Box 37)
      - General (Box 38)
      - Correspondence (Box 38)
      - Correspondence and Memoranda September 1973-January 1974 (Box 38)
      - Lease Inquiries (Box 38)
      - Leonard Dobbs Files
        - General, 3 folders (Box 38)
        - February 1968-April 1973 (Box 38)
        - May-June 1973 (Box 38)
        - July 1973 (Box 38)
        - July-August 1973 (Box 38)
        - January-August 1974 (Box 38)
      - Richard Kughn Files (Box 38)
      - Service Contracts (Box 38)
    - Yonkers Electric (Box 38)
  - Northridge (Milwaukee, WI)
    - Lease (Box 39)
    - Residual Property (Box 39)
    - Logo, Merchants Association, Miscellaneous (Box 39)
    - Prospective Tenants (Box 39)
    - Public Relations and Projections (Box 39)
    - Architecture (Box 39)
    - Boston Store (Box 39)
    - Federated Construction (Box 39)
    - Financial (Box 39)
    - Photographs (Box 39)
    - Correspondence 1967-1971 (Box 39)
  - Southridge (Milwaukee, WI)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 40)
    - J.C. Penney (Box 40)
    - Plans (Box 40)
    - Prospective Tenants (Box 40)
    - Public Relations, 2 folders (Box 40)
    - Gimbel's (Box 40)
    - Kohl's Department Store (Box 40)
    - Lease (Box 40)
    - Progress Reports (Box 40)
    - Projections (Box 40)
  - Stamford Town Center, Stamford, Conn. (Box 41)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 41)
  - Leasing Plans
    - Briarwood (Box 41)
    - Eastridge (Box 41)
    - Fairlane (Box 41)
    - Hilltop (Box 41)
    - Lakeforest (Box 41)
    - Lakeside (Box 41)
    - Northridge (Box 41)
    - Queens Center (Box 41)
    - Southland (Box 41)
    - Southridge (Box 41)
    - Sunvalley (Box 41)
    - Westfarms (Box 41)
    - Woodfield (Box 41)
    - Woodland (Box 41)
  - Site Plans
    - Briarwood (Box 41)
    - Eastridge (Box 41)
    - Engineering and Research Institute (Ann Arbor, MI) (Box 41)
    - Fairfax (Box 41)
    - Fairlane (Box 41)
    - Hilltop (Box 41)
    - Lakeforest (Box 41)
    - Lakeside (Box 41)
    - Marley Station (Box 41)
    - Meadowood (Box 41)
    - Nashville (Box 41)
    - Northridge (Box 41)
    - Oakland (Box 41)
    - Parsippany (Box 41)
    - Redwood Shores (Box 41)
    - Short Hills, 2 folders (Box 41)
      (include photographs)
    - Southland (Box 41)
    - Southridge (Box 41)
    - Stamford (Box 41)
    - Stoneridge (Box 41)
    - Sunvalley (Box 41)
    - Westfarms (Box 41)
    - Woodfield (Box 41)
    - Woodland (Box 41)
    - Yonkers (Box 41)
  - Shopping Center Scrapbooks Photo Albums, Architects' Proposals, and Miscellaneous Reports
    - 163rd Street Shopping Center (Miami) Scrapbook (Box 42)
    - J. L. Hudson/Eastland Center, East Detroit, MI Scrapbook (Box 42)
    - Kenneth C. Welch, Architect, Old Orchard / Marshall Field & Company Shopping Center (Box 42)
    - Kenneth C. Welch, Architect, Southdale Regional Shopping Center 1956-1957 (Box 42)
    - Bridgewater Town Center Booklet, Taubman Company (proposed New Jersey shopping center) (Box 42)
    - Guest Books (event or occasion uncertain), 4 volumes (Box 42)
    - Development Opportunities/Baychester Realty/Baychester Properties April 1968 (Box 43)
    - Research Report/Battelle Memorial Institute September 29, 1967 (Box 43)
    - Societe Internationale D'Etudes/Geotechnical Report/Brussels West Shopping Center March 29, 1967 (Box 43)
    - Engineering Report on Maple Boulevard, Ann Arbor February 1967: Prepared by: Engineering Division-Department of Public Works-Ann Arbor (Box 43)
    - Structured Sculpture, Galerie Chalette (Box 43)
    - California Profit Opportunities, Published for Agriculture, Commerce & Ind. By: Economic Development Agency State of California (Box 43)